
An encoding scheme is a mapping between a sequence of bits and a human understandable character, such as 'a', '1', or '['. An encoding scheme is
simply a mapping that can be used to either 1) encode characters into bytes or 2) decode bytes into characters
- To encode means to convert into a coded form, such as bytes. To encode text that is already in ascii, take each letter and substitute the
  corresponding sequence of bytes. 
    - ascii maps 8-bits to a character
- To decode means to convert from a coded form into something that's understandable by humans. To decode bytes into ascii, take each byte and
  substitute the corresponding character

One byte can represent a maximum of 256 values [0, 255]. That isn't sufficient for languages that contain more than 256 characters (e.g. Chinese).
There are encodings that use 2 bytes to rectify this problem (e.g. BIG-5), which can represent 65,536 characters! But that still wasn't enough, so
Unicode was created. So how many bits does Unicode use to encode a character? None! Unicode is not an encoding!

Unicode defines a table of 1,114,112 code points for characters (e.g. code point 65 stands for 'A'). 2 bytes wasn't enough for that many code points,
and 3 bytes is enough but is awkward to use, so 4 bytes is the comfortable minimum. But using 4 bytes for every character would waste a LOT of space!
To solve this, there are several ways to encode Unicode code points into bits (Yes, CODE POINTS are encoded into bits). 
- UTF-32 is an encoding that encodes all Unicode code points (into bits) using 4 bytes. It's easy to understand, but wastes a lot of space
- UTF-16 and UTF-8 are variable-length encodings.
    - In UTF-8, if a character CAN be represented in a single byte, it will be encoded in a single byte. If it requires 2 bytes, UTF-8 will use 2
      bytes, etc. UTF-8 has an elaborate system to use the highest bit in a byte to show how many bytes a character consists of. However, if these
      signal bits are used often, it can waste space
    - UTF-16 follows the same principles, but uses 2 bytes minimum per code-point-to-bytes encoding
Different Unicode encodings can create entirely different sequences of bits, depending on the characters that are being encoded. Thus, the choice
between UTF-8, UTF-16, and UTF-32 is based on space efficiency, not on which code points will or won't be encoded.
